LUIS ROCHA:

DESIGNER | FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER.

luisrochadev.com luisrochaphoto.com luisrochadev@gmail.com (619) 699-9854

SUMMARY

Frontend web developer with a passion for design. Skilled in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Angular. Proficient with the Adobe Creative Suite. Obsessed with producing intuitive and aesthetically pleasing user experiences. Clean, responsive, mobile-first design above all else.

SKILLS

Front-end development (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
Front-end frameworks and libraries (Angular, Bootstrap, EJS)
Back-end development (Node.JS, Express)
Testing & deployment (Mocha, Heroku)
Tools (Git, GitHub, NPM, Gulp)
Adobe Creative Suite (PS, Lightroom, InDesign, etc)

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER - Interact Intranet

June 2016 - October 2016

Designed, developed, and tested responsive pages for a global B2B SaaS company with data metrics in mind. Analyzed UI/UX design of existing pages for responsive layout for improved usability. Built sophisticated and elegant user interfaces with cross-browser functionality. Ensured high front-end performance.

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER - San Franpsycho

January 2015 - September 2015

Increased social media follower count by 40% and customer engagement by 60% in the span of 6 months. Curated relevant content for posts in order reach the company's ideal customers at a fast pace. Developed and carried out marketing strategy proven by metrics.

STAFF PHOTOGRAPHER - San Franpsycho

August 2013 - September 2015

Developed and defined brand's current visual aesthetic/identity. Conceptualized photoshoots that showcased fashions as

effectively as possible. Shot/edited multiple lifestyle photos a week for use on various social media platforms.

FOUNDER, PHOTOGRAPHER: Luis Rocha Photography

January 2011 - Present

Self-employed freelancer. Pro-actively sought out potential clients and secured contracts with major brands and music

festivals including Outside Lands, Coachella, EDC, and more. Combined technical proficiency with artistry to create images of people, places, events and products.

EDUCATION

GALVANIZE San Francisco, CA 24-Week Web Development Program